Well, everybody, welcome to NFA Live.
Looks like the inflation data is out and
it is not too awful. So, to help me
break that down, I've got Guy from Coin
Bureau and Coin Finance and Coin Korea
and Coin Everything. Thank you, Guy, for
stopping by and Ben into the
cryptoverse. How's How are you guys
doing? How you doing, guy?
>> Yeah, I'm well, thanks Rob. I'm well.
I've had a couple of weeks back home in
the UK and now uh back home again in
Dubai. So, uh yeah, it's all good.
>> All good. And Ben, after two weeks off,
how things been for you?
>> Good. Just um yeah, was out of town for
the last week on a vacation. So, feel
pretty good. Bitcoin's the same price as
I left it. So, here we are.
>> See, this is why you left it and you let
it go just chop sideways and that's
fine. So everybody, before we get into
it, I'd like to remind everybody that uh
there's a little conference going on in
Miami 20th to the 22nd of November. And
we've got uh quite a few people who are
speaking. There's this guy named Ben and
uh Chem Mark Yusco, Alicia Rostani,
James Czech, which I got to tell you,
that guy puts out some really good
information. I'd like to hear what he
has to say. Mike Mcloone, this guy named
Guy Turner, Gareth, David, Jason Bazino,
even Aldo Felichi,
CryptoKid, Tom Crown, and Matt Crosby
rounding it all out. So, like I've said
before, I think everybody deserves a
vacation after this brutal brute, well,
not so fair market. So, join us in
Miami. Should be a fun time. And just so
you know, pricing for the tickets are
due to go up at some point. But good
news for you today, if you're watching
this video, you have a chance to win a
couple of tickets. So, there's a link in
the description. Fill out this form and
at the end of this live stream, we're
going to add or pick some people at
random for two basic standards and one
pro today. And uh just so we keep
everything even and we know that this
isn't rigged like all other elections,
I'll be putting this into a nice little
picker that uh Claude drew up for me.
All right, everybody. So, that would be
the shameless plug for uh the
conference. Let's get into the numbers.
So, this just came out
what uh 30 minutes ago or so. Looks like
um well, first of all, yesterday Walsh
came out and said that he is not raising
rates. Uh but there's a couple of uh
members of the uh team that looks like
they're desenting. I'll talk to guy
about that. But right now we've got PC
price index for June. It fell 0.1%.
So that's great. Uh month over month at
3.7 uh year-over-year. The core PC price
index increased 0.1. So kind of like a
wash. GDP grew at an annualized rate of
1.5% and initial jobless claims at
197,000. I think that's uh pretty low
numbers, but take a look at it. And the
market has uh responded. Looks like
Bitcoin likes that. Let me refresh this
real quick.
Last hour or so, so not too bad. And uh
let's break this down and get into it.
But first, I want to ask Guy Guy, you
put out a nice little snippet here on a
short. You talked about three things
that Wsh came out and said that were
concerning. So tell us about that and
then we'll break down a little bit of
the uh economic macro with Ben. But what
were the three things that you talked
about here?
>> Yeah, sure. Um, and remember, of course,
this is, uh, you know, this is Kevin
Walsh, very, very much has a very
different attitude, um, to what the Fed
uh, you know, what the Fed should be
saying and doing, um, especially as as
it concerns, you know, forward guidance
and stuff. So, um, yeah, I mean, the
third sort of thing that he said was,
uh, you know, that the Fed is is very
much focused on forcing inflation down
to that 2% target no matter the cost.
Um, and it was interesting what he he
said around this. He said that you know
five years of high prices have made made
people kind of accept
>> 3% as as normal. Um so you know it's
it's kind of this this idea of shifting
baseline theory. You know people are
kind of getting used to 3% inflation now
whereas actually you know the Fed's
mandate is a whole percentage lower than
that and that's what they should be
aiming at. Um and he also said um there
are no soft targets. So what he meant by
that was that he will that the Fed will
keep rates high enough um until they
have an effect of an effect on inflation
until they bring inflation down even if
you know that causes that causes pain
you know that hurts um that hurts family
budgets or or whatever because I think
you know he like many others recognizes
just how insidious a force inflation is
and you you know you have to stay on top
of it so I think that's something to
bear in mind you and and it's kind of,
you know, it's it's it's along the same
sort of lines as what Powell would
always say as well.
>> Um, but I guess that shows that, you
know, one thing hasn't changed from from
the transition in in chair and that's
still the idea that 2% is the inflation
target and that is what inflation needs
to be at um no matter no matter the
cost. Um and that and then and that kind
of leads on to the second thing he said
that you know interest rates could
actually go up as we as you mentioned
Rob three members of that 12 person FOMC
uh board dissented and their descent was
they wanted to raise rates right now um
and the phrase uh that Walsh used was um
that this is the beginning of the story
and not the end. So, you know, that
means for anyone who's got, you know,
carrying debt or hoping that mortgage
rates are going to go down or whatever,
you know, sorry, that isn't going to
happen. So, the spectre of rate rises is
still very much alive and I think it's
probably, you know, a question of sooner
rather than later. Um, but the um the
first one was perhaps more concerning
than the other two. And that is, you
know, again, this feeds into what Kevin
Walsh has been saying kind of ever since
he took the reigns is that they're not
going to do forward guidance. They're
not going to give any early warnings um
you know, about what they're they won't
give any hints about what they're going
to do. Um and uh the phrase, um he used,
you know, to investors was to play the
ball and not the referee. Um which I
which I quite liked.
>> That's pretty good. I like that.
>> That's pretty good. Um I I like to think
that's a nice football analogy. Um you
know in time just for the end of the
World Cup. Um so but you know what this
means is that without the sort of early
warnings without that forward guidance
that we were used to under Powell it
means that everything you know all
investors all markets everyone um the
smart money the dumb money and everyone
in between is just left guessing until
the actual decision is announced. And of
course that means uncertainty and that
means volatility. Um so it's kind of
making it's kind of making it very
tricky to get an idea of where they
might be headed. Um we obviously have
tools like the you know the Fed watch
and what have you. But yeah with the
lack of forward guidance it very much
becomes a bit of a guessing game until
we know it. So yeah that makes it that
makes it that little bit harder
>> I think. So well said guy. Well said.
And then talking about those tools, we
can see here that this was I didn't
refresh my my browser. I want to leave
this here. The target rate 350 375. They
called it. They nailed it. I think a lot
of people said that they were not going
to raise rates. Wash was going to stay
the same. The only one that said that it
would actually might happen was Citadel
Securities, which I thought was kind of
interesting as they came out and said,
"Yeah, it's going to be a surprise race.
You guys just watch and see." And of
course, the numbers don't lie. However,
taking a look here, the next meeting we
have is coming up on 16th of September,
2026. And just like what you said, guy,
uh we've got three denters. We can see
that uh the rates looks like they would
be going up 375 to 400. Let me refresh
that. Maybe things have changed a little
bit. Who knows? A little bit, but it's a
6040 split. It looks like we might raise
rates. So, this would come back to Ben.
What do you think here? if we start to
raise rates and we start to talk about
this and that expectation is coming in
into the markets. I did like this video
you put out. This was your last one.
Well, when will the Fed raise rates and
you had a nice uh overlay and you took a
look at the inflation year-over-year?
And he took also a look at the uh
two-year treasuries as they are lining
up. But the two-year Treasury, which the
Fed has been tracking, you talked about
how this has actually increased, and
this is where you think that the Fed
rates will actually go as they will
increase. So, as you see the numbers
that are there, what's your thoughts
here, Ben, moving forward?
>> Yeah. Um, back in what, like last or
earlier this year, the Fed funds rate
was lower than the 2-year yield. Uh, but
that's now changed. It's now higher than
the 2-year yield. And so what that what
that sort of means is if you believe in
the neutral rate this abstract concept
from which when the Fed funds rate is
above the 2-year yield the argument is
that we are in restrictive territory in
terms of monetary policy and when it's
below it's more accommodative. So
earlier this year and you know for the
last year or two the Fed funds rate has
been above the 2-year yield I believe.
Um,
but that's changed now. And and so you
could argue that while it was above it,
there was this you could pretty clearly
see higher risk assets bleeding to lower
risk assets. That's why things like
Bitcoin dominance were going up and
whatnot. But now it's flipped back,
right? Now it's flipped back and the
two-year yield is is actually above the
Fed funds rate even though the Fed funds
rate hasn't gone anywhere in a while. So
the argument now is that because the
neutral rate is a moving target, the you
we're no longer in restrictive
territory. And if that's the case, then
you know the labor market might start to
heat back up again. You can already see
the unemployment rate has been trending
down. Initial claims have been trending
down. That could put pressure on wage
inflation, which could put pressure on
overall inflation, headline inflation.
And so I think what you're seeing happen
is the Fed's unwilling to raise rates.
Now, the bond market is revoling. You
know, if you look at the 30-year yield,
it's breaking out to new highs. The
10-year yield's probably heading back up
to where it was in October 2023. When
yields were breaking out starting in
July, they started to really move up in
July of 2023 until October of 2023. The
S&P ended up getting like a 10% drop.
So, I I think that we are likely going
to get a rate hike this year. I don't
know exactly what month. I mean,
September seems like a a likely
candidate, but I think you will have
one. And and then I think people are
going to get really spooked by it
because, you know, a rate hike after
rate cuts kind of hits a little bit
different than just a rate hike, you
know, kind of a few years ago.
>> Um, but I I think it would be kind of a
the perfect narrative for everything
playing out just the way it always does,
right? like the stock market gets a
correction in the back half of the
midterm year. Bitcoin finds a market
cycle bottom and it's all because people
are freaking out about the Fed's raising
rates and oh, you know what's what's
going to happen now. Um, so I think I
think if you need a narrative, it's
there. Not that you need one.
>> We all need a narrative. That's the
whole thing. We we appreciate those. So,
right now, we can see that uh this is
essentially where we are at. I still
think that we're going to see a little
bit of uh of rate hikes and even I think
one of the one of the Fed uh chair no to
the one of the Fed members was on
Squawkbox yesterday. Uh I forget his
name, but he talked about and he was the
most doubbish person. He said even I can
see a case for raising rates. So if
people are expecting things to just keep
dropping, I don't think it's actually
going to happen. So evaluate that and
put that into your uh your buying or
selling strategy. I think we've got a
little bit of a rocky road going into
and out of the midterm years. So, thank
you gentlemen for that. I just want to
see where we were actually at with
macro. And that would uh really conclude
the macro part. The next part we're
going to talk about before we get into
the drawing is just an anecdotal story.
And I like this one because uh it kind
of shows you where where things are at.
Now, if you're a technical trader, this
has nothing to do with, but I got to
tell you, this was a pretty good one. I
had a I had lunch with a friend last
week and he talked about how he sold his
truck and he's a farmer. Sold his truck
and he was going to put it all into
Bitcoin. But this guy's a little bit
different. He was in a Bitcoin in 2013
and he's been holding for quite some
time and had some pretty good gains and
uh yeah, he's doing not too bad, I
think. But he sold his truck. He took a
loan out to buy another truck because
he's a farmer. He needs that. and uh and
I and he says he goes I'm going to buy
Bitcoin this week. He just bought
recently. So my question to you and uh
guy I'll start with you. Do you think
this was a was a good move for him to do
in the long run or the short run or do
you think this was just crazy talk? And
then what do you hear about as far as
like people around you and the sentiment
for crypto right now, Bitcoin specific?
>> Yeah. So So he sold the truck. So he
He now does not have a truck.
>> No, no, no. So, he sold his truck. He
got 55k out of it. It's very nice truck.
Ford F-150. One of my favorites. And uh
he took that 55K and dumped it into
Bitcoin. Blum sum. Okay.
>> And then he took a loan out to buy
another truck because he needs a new
truck and he's like, I'd like to get a
new truck anyhow. So, he's got a loan at
whatever it is, I know, 6.5% or
something like that over five years.
So, would this be like a good strategy
for him to do or this is just a crazy
talk?
>> Well, I Yeah, I just wanted to check
because I mean, so he's not without a
truck at the moment because as you say,
he's a farmer and he needs one. So, he
has he has got a truck. He's just
rotated some of the money that he made
on the last one out of it. Okay.
>> Exactly.
>> Okay. Well, that was good because if he
if he was without a truck, I was going
to say he's the biggest fool alive, but
um that's good. Okay. Um, yeah. I mean,
I I don't love the idea of, however well
you're doing, I don't love the idea of
taking out a loan to buy well to buy
anything really. But, you know, a specul
a highly speculative and very volatile
asset like Bitcoin. You know, taking out
a loan to buy that is not something I
would ever advise anyone to do. Even
though I believe that in the long term
uh Bitcoin will start going back up
again and I'm I'm kind of on board with
what Ben said about, you know, the the
way the cycle playing out and uh
possibly towards the end of this year,
you know, we could see um we could see
prices start to rise again. So, I guess
on that timeline, he's he's bought at a
good time. But like I say, I feel very
uncomfortable with the idea that he's
done it with borrowed money. Um because
I kind of feel, you know, I kind of feel
he's sort of okay, he was in it in 2013,
made a nice profit out of it. You know
what? Because he won last time doesn't
necessarily mean you'll win again. So
all you know I've got to hope that he's
got other ways of paying that loan back
if Bitcoin doesn't do what he wants to
do because I I think getting in debt to
buy a highly risky speculative asset
like Bitcoin is is not is not the way
forward personally.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I can see that for sure. And
I remember like uh it's it's for for
some people would I remember this
happened in 2021
where people would take out massive
loans and go into altcoins and just lose
everything. And when he did it, it was
just interesting to me because he has
another stream of revenue which is he
has real estate, he has crops and things
like that. So he's like, "Look, I just
wanted this to come in." And I just
thought it was an interesting story and
a different timing because he talked
about how
>> he did a big a big move in 2018 as well
when Bitcoin was at $3,000 and he said
it worked out pretty well. So we'll see
how it works. I just wanted to put this
story out because I want to reference
this in the next two three years or so
and see where we're actually at and if
60,000 was an awful mistake or a pretty
good strategy. We'll see.
>> Oh man. I mean I I really hope it works
out for him because that would be that
would be amazing. you know, if it goes
if it goes to 200k or whatever and he,
you know, quadruples his money or
whatever it is, great. I really I really
hope that turns out to be the case. But,
you know, um I guess it kind of it kind
of suggests to me that we live very much
in that sort of culture now where I, you
know, I don't think there there is a
gambling element to it, but it just
seems like so many people are just like
to hell with it. I'm just gonna I'm
gonna spin that wheel. I'm gonna take
that risk and I think that says a lot
about the world we live in and uh you
know the the the values that we have. Um
but yeah, I mean I think now you hear a
story like that and most people are like
you know they might be like me and it's
like well it's not a great idea but I
think most people be like okay good luck
to you. Whereas if you'd said that to
someone 30 years ago they would be like
what the guy's insane. Um, so yeah, we
the world has changed a lot.
>> 30 years ago, people would say, "You
know what you need to do? Collect a
pension and then just put everything
away in your savings account. You'll be
just fine." Anyhow,
Ben, last question. Last question for
you. What do you think about that that
strategy? Would you ever do something
like that? It seems kind of crazy right
now.
>> I mean, I think um probably depends on
his timeline, right? Like if he's if his
timeline's long enough, it probably
works out. If it's not, probably
doesn't, you know? Hey, one of my uh
someone I you know learned from a long
time ago, he would tell me about like
with stocks and stuff like don't ever
buy don't ever buy the S&P unless you
know unless you are have the ability to
hold it for at least a few years. Like
if you if you're going to buy it and
like it has to go to a certain price or
it can't go down in like the next six
months or something and you're buying
it, you're probably better off not
buying it. But if you can hold it for,
you know, I mean, I think with the stock
market, it was like five or 10 years,
then there's no reason to worry that
much about like what the stock market's
going to do next month. So, I mean, I
think with Bitcoin, obviously, there's
this four-year cycle stuff looming over
our heads and and, you know, sort of um
would say that the price could go lower,
but at the same time, normally just
buying Bitcoin second half of the
midterm year works out relatively well
as long as you can like not panic um if
there is that if there is that drop in
Q4. I mean I I typically prefer to DCA
in to Bitcoin um rather than rather than
lump sum just because I mean you know
the stock market doesn't drop usually
like 50% overnight whereas we've seen
Bitcoin do that many times.
>> Um so it's a little bit different you
know than than investing in the stock
market. So I mean I hope it works out
for him. Um, probably going to be, you
know, maybe some a few more scary times
this year before hopefully things are
things look a little bit better.
>> Yep. Well said. So, we'll see how it all
works out. I like to reference this
story as time goes on because it's
always interesting to get that
perspective, especially as we are in the
bare market, midterm lows. And that's it
for today, everybody. So, if you like
today's video, thumbs up, subscribe, all
that great stuff. There's a link to to
Ben's channel and guys channels plural.
You can check those out. Now, let's get
into the last part, which will be draw
and giveaway. So, everybody, thanks so
much for putting in the information
to attend the conference. I'll be there.
Guy will be there. This will be the
first time we've all been together in
the same place. It's kind of strange.
So, maybe we'll do an NFA live, like
really live. So, you filled this out
already. Let's see who we got. All
right, I'm not going to show everybody's
email because that would be a tragic
error, but let me just do this. I'm
going to
pick all the first names.
And
>> Rob, you're awfully dressed up today.
Yeah, you know, I try to I try to make a
good impression on some people. Try to
look a little decent. Yeah. Well, you
got Ben, when you got 10 kids, you know,
it's it ain't easy. Got to do all those
things that you got.
>> Let's see. So, I'm going to put these
names in
and we're going to draw three winners. H
remove dup. Actually, no, no, no. Yeah,
let's do three winners. The last winner
will be the one for the higher tier.
Uh I forgot what it's called. Ben has it
at the pro tier. So let's draw those
winners. We're going to remove the
duplicate entries. I know some of you
tried to cheat and if you ain't
cheating, you ain't trying. So good job.
Winner one, Dylan, David, and Anthony.
So I have your names. Let me do a
screenshot of that.
I will be emailing you personally from
my account and I will be asking you for
one bitcoin and I will send you two
back. Obviously not. So expect those
emails to be come out. And again
everybody those will be the last drawing
for the ITC conference. Again I'd like
to see everybody there as many people as
we can to get there. We got some pretty
good uh speakers. So uh let's all hang
out in Miami. And that's it for this
port. Now let's go into a little Q&A
session. You can ask Guy and Ben
anything and they'll answer all your
questions and then we'll get the heck
out of here. All right. So, what do we
have?
Congrats winners.
>> There's of us. There's dozens of us
left, Rob.
>> There's
Exactly.
There's only so many. Congrats all the
winners. I always hated that like like
when I would like like lose in sports.
I'm like, "Yeah, congratulations." But
you don't really really mean it. You're
like, "Damn it. Why couldn't I have won
that one? Thank you. Oh, Gassi the says
no ladies as a speakers.
This is a What's What's the We're
probably announcing a couple like in the
next week that are that are women
actually.
>> It's not my fault. It's just that they
the people we just haven't had hasn't
aligned yet, but I think we have some
now.
>> Very nice. Hello from Maldees selling
tickets.
Uh, well, what's your Well, Hyperliquid,
this is one of the few altcoins that
actually
went up and had a nice ROI. What's your
thoughts on hype guy? I think you're
more of the altcoin person as opposed to
say Ben and derivatives. So,
>> yeah, I mean, I think I think it's been
sort of struggling a little bit
recently. There does seem to be a bit
more competition. I think lighter is is
maybe giving hyperlquid a bit of a run
for its money but I mean it is still it
is still very much the venue especially
for kind of out of hours trading isn't
it? I mean like the you know this Iran
this Iran conflict sort of I think was a
big kind of proving thing you know
because uh when when stuff was happening
out of hours and people were able to
speculate on oil and what have you but
you know of certainly of of the major
altcoin projects it's one of the it's
one of the few that has that that's
found sort of product market fit people
love it generates a ton of revenue I
mean I think I saw somewhere you know
Hyperlquid alone is responsible for
you know, if not the majority, then
certainly a huge chunk of overall app
revenue in crypto, which shows us that
we've got a long way to go. But I yeah,
I think it's and and of course they're
doing I think they're still doing
buybacks of hype with profits. So,
>> I don't see why unless something unless
something bad happens, unless it gets
hacked or has some sort of exploit or
something like that, I think it's going
to I think it's going to stick around. I
I know Lewis, my uh colleague here at
Coin Bureau, um has uh has said that
he's going to buy a whole load more of
it if it uh what did he say? He's
investing $5,000 into hype every time it
drops 10%. Um so, you know, there's some
there's some conviction for you. But
yeah, I think I think long-term hype
should do well.
>> Very nice. Yeah, I got a little bit of
that. Hopefully, it does well. How about
this one? What's the chances
percentage-wise that the bottom is
already in for Bitcoin? Anyone want to
take that one? Bottom already in. I
think we got some time to go, but that's
me.
>> I mean, I think anything's possible.
Like, you you can't ever ever get too
confident in, you know, a low being
either in or not. I would say it's
probably less than 50% would be my guess
that it's already in. I I think the most
likely time is the fourth quarter of the
year. Um, that's what that's what it
normally is. Um, and I I think the hard
thing about this year is like the, you
know, like the constant mental
gymnastics around that like
>> Yeah.
>> And and even back in like early this
year when we were talking about how
Bitcoin usually finds low in February
and then bounces, people are like, "Oh,
no, just because it usually does that,
this time's going to be different." And
then it did the same thing anyways,
right? And then in May, we even did a we
I think we did a um like a live stream.
I think you I think Rob titled it like
sell a mango away and how Bitcoin then
normally sells off again into the summer
and people are like no just that just
because it always happens it doesn't
mean it will happen again and then it
just happened again anyways. So like I I
I it's not like I don't understand where
people are coming from but I'm also of
the opinion if it's not broke don't fix
it, you know? So like hey if the market
wants to prove me wrong let it prove me
wrong until then I'm just going to
assume it's going to keep doing what it
always does.
>> Yeah I think so. guy. Same thing or
>> Yeah. Yeah. Not much to add there. I
agree.
>> Yeah.
>> It's It's a funny I think we live in the
matrix. It seemed like things just keep
going round about almost Groundhog Day
like, but we'll see.
>> Uh here's a good one and it's a it's a
question I actually have. What's the
reason strategy is not buying the lows?
I don't really understand. Strategy does
a great job of buying the the the tops,
that's for sure. and uh also selling
selling some of the bottoms. But uh
anything you guys are tracking over
there at Coin Bureau guy?
>> Well, I just think that strategy's been
kind of very much caught out by the fact
that that I think they just
overleveraged isn't the word, I don't
think, but they I think they just got
too ambitious. you know, issuing is
issuing things like stretch, this STRC
preferred stock or whatever that pays a
pretty hefty dividend and giving
themselves these obligations to meet you
know these dividend obligations to meet
etc. which means they have to have cash
or you know you know they they have to
find a way of raising cash and either
they do that by dilute diluting MSTR
holders which is what they've been
mostly doing or selling Bitcoin which
they've done you know they did a little
bit of it and the market really did not
like that at all. Um, so I guess you
know probably the plan was to keep on
accumulating through the lows if uh, you
know, unless they just mistimed the
lows. But yeah, I think I think
basically they've their strategy was
um, you know, over complicated, a bit
ambitious, just buy just buy and buy and
hold Bitcoin. But instead, you know,
they they found this so-called infinite
money glitch. And guess what? It didn't
quite work out like that. And now the
market is basically telling them, "No,
you you can't go and buy more uh Bitcoin
right now because you need to have cash
on hand in order to honor those dividend
obligations and everything else." Um
otherwise people are going to people are
going to, you know, dump MSTR. People
are going to lose faith in Bitcoin or
whatever. So I think kind of they've
they've had their hand forced in a way
is my best guess. Just one more one more
reason why Treasury companies will bleed
to Bitcoin over the long term in my
opinion.
>> Yeah, unfortunately. So, and I have to
apologize. I uh I thought that they
bought the high, but they did not. They
bought at 117K. So, I stand corrected.
All right. So, let's see what else we
have.
This is a good one. Ben, there's not
enough gold stars available for you. You
excel as a human being. Thank you very
very much for all your hard work. It is
such a dichotomy. It's such a difference
between like the live streams of what's
being said about Ben as opposed to like
on X and what's being said about Ben.
It's like Dr. Jackal and Mr. Height.
It's amazing to me every time.
>> Yeah. No, I mean it's been like a uh
imagine imagine how I've I mean I don't
really I don't really feel um a lot of
emotions towards comments anymore on X,
but man like three four years ago. I
mean I was just like a bucket of misery
like listening to these reading these
comments that people would say about me
and then and then now I look back and
I'm like no I I I I'm happy that I said
what I said back then and and and you
know I'm I'm not going to apologize for
it.
>> Yeah. See, you just got to take just
take a take a page out of Guy Guy's
book. You just post great information
constantly over at Coin Bureau. It's
always like good stuff just about the
news, just the facts, ma'am, and that's
it. And there's very like like little
little back and forth. All right.
And I think that's Yeah, I think that's
it. Haters are hard of hearing
meta planets. I think we I'm the same
way. the digital asset treasuries,
especially for Ethereum. Oof, pretty
brutal. We'll see if that goes.
>> Well, look at um Jack Malice. He just
stepped away from 21, didn't he? There
was a there was a British one that I'd
never heard of called Satsuma or
something like that. Just wound wound it
up. I'm sure there will be more. I'm
sure there will be more because it's
it's the sort of thing like it can work
for, you know, it can work for one. I
think I I think strategy will be fine.
Um you know, they've had their they've
they've had their wings clipped a little
bit, but they'll be okay. Um, but all
these smaller ones, I mean, it was a it
was an accident. It was a disaster
waiting to happen. So, you know, the
sooner the sooner they just the sooner
the crap ones just go and die and, you
know, put all their Bitcoin back on the
market so so as you know, other people
can accumulate it, the better. Really,
>> that's spoken like a a a true multicycle
veteran. All right, everybody. That's it
for today. If you like today's video,
thumbs up, subscribe, all that good
stuff. links in the description for
everything. Again, we'll see you guys in
November, all three of us in Miami.
Thanks so much everybody. See you in the
next one. Adios.